Guide to the Susan H. Douglas political Americana collection, [1783?]-1961.
Douglas, Susan H. Political Americana Collection, [1783?]-1961
- Series XI. Posters
  - For Vice-President: John A. Logan, 1884; 2214.PO0035 (Box 85)
  - Theodore Roosevelt: Republican Candidate for Vice-President, 1900; 2214.PO0036 (Box 98)
  - Benjamin Harrison: Republican Candidate for President of the United States, ca. 1892; 2214.PO0037 (Box 98)
  - Whitelaw Reid. Republican Candidate for Vice President, ca. 1892; 2214.PO0038 (Box 98)
  - Garfield and Arthur: Republican Candidates for 1880, ca. 1880; 2214.PO0039 (Box 98)
  - Hancock and English: Democratic Candidates for 1880, ca. 1880; 2214.PO0040 (Box 98)
  - Richard M. Nixon, ca. 1952; 2214.PO0041 (Box 95)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, ca. 1952; 2214.PO0042 (Box 95)
  - Herbert Hoover for President, Charles Curtis for Vice-President, 1928; 2214.PO0043 (Box 85)
  - Democratic Nominations: Vote Every Star, Keep Good Government, ca. 1928; 2214.PO0044 (Box 98)
  - For President: Alfred E. Smith, 1928; 2214.PO0045 (Box 85)
  - Winfield S. Hancock, Democratic Candidate for President, ca. 1880; 2214.PO0048 (Box 95)
  - Wm. H. English, Democratic Candidate for Vice-President, ca. 1880; 2214.PO0049 (Box 95)
  - Vote the Republican Ticket, 1908; 2214.PO0050 (Box 98)
  - Wendell Willkie: Official photograph, 1940; 2214.PO0052a (Box 95)
  - Wendell Willkie: Official photograph, 1940; 2214.PO0052b (Box 95)
  - Harriman: In Step ... Can Win, 1956; 2214.PO0058 (Box 85)
  - Stevenson For President, 1956; 2214.PO0060 (Box 85)
  - Stevenson for President, ca. 1956; 2214.PO0061 (Box 95)
  - Happy Birthday Ike, 1956; 2214.PO0062 (Box 85)
  - Keep America Strong: Re-elect Eisenhower, 1956; 2214.PO0063 (Box 85)
  - Re-Elect Richard M. Nixon, ca. 1956; 2214.PO0064 (Box 95)
  - Re-elect Dwight D. Eisenhower, ca. 1956; 2214.PO0065 (Box 95)
  - Vote for Peace, Vote for Prosperity, Vote for Ike, ca. 1956; 2214.PO0066 (Box 95)
  - You win when you vote for Ike and Dick, ca. 1956; 2214.PO0067 (Box 95)
  - Vote as You Think- but Vote Nov. 6, 1956; 2214.PO0068 (Box 95)
  - America Needs Nixon - Lodge, 1960; 2214.PO0076 (Box 85)
  - Vote Nixon - Lodge: Experience Counts!, 1960; 2214.PO0077 (Box 85)
  - Kennedy for President: Leadership for the 60's, 1960; 2214.PO0078 (Box 85)
  - Kennedy - Johnson: two great Democrats, 1960; 2214.PO0079 (Map-case -)
  - Leadership for the 60's: Kennedy - Johnson, 1960; 2214.PO0080 (Map-case -)
- Series XII Prints
  Prints: This series is primarily comprised of smaller political portrait images intended for public or home display, although Mrs. Douglas also included a number of two-page images from newspaper center-spreads. 19th century lithographs and wood engravings make up a significant proportion of this category.
  - Old Tippecanoe has Come Out in the West, ca. 1840; 2214.PR0001 (Box 86)
  - For President: Dwight D. Eisenhower; For Vice President: Richard M. Nixon, 1952; 2214.PR0002 (Box 86)
  - Gen. Grant and Family, 1869; 2214.PR0003 (Box 86)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Portrait, 2214.PR0004 (Box 86)
  - George Washington Portrait, 2214.PR0005 (Box 86)
  - Abraham Lincoln Portrait, 2214.PR0006 (Box 86)
  - George Washington: Official Bicentennial Likeness, 1932; 2214.PR0007 (Box 86)
  - Washington at Trenton, 1932; 2214.PR0008 (Box 86)
  - Washington at Valley Forge, 1932; 2214.PR0009 (Box 86)
  - Washington at Mount Vernon, 1772; 2214.PR0010 (Box 86)
  - George Washington, 1932; 2214.PR0011 (Box 86)
  - To the Memory of W. Henry Harrison, 1841; 2214.PR0012 (Box 86)
  - John Adams. Second President of the United States, 2214.PR0013 (Box 101)
  - John Quincy Adams: Sixth President of the United States, 2214.PR0014 (Box 86)
  - Grand, National, Democratic Banner: Press Onward, 1848; 2214.PR0015 (Box 86)
  - Henry Clay. Nominated for Eleventh President of the United States, 1844; 2214.PR0016 (Box 86)
  - Henry Clay, 2214.PR0017 (Box 101)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.PR0018 (Box -)
  - Henry Clay of Kentucky, 1844; 2214.PR0019 (Box 86)
  - Henry Clay: Grand National Whig Banner, 1844; 2214.PR0020 (Box 86)
  - Hon. Schuyler Colfax: The Nation's Choice for Vice President of the U.S., 1868; 2214.PR0021 (Box 86)
  - George M. Dallas, 1844; 2214.PR0022 (Box 86)
  - National Democratic Banner, 1860; 2214.PR0023 (Box TBD)
  - The Presidents of the United States: Washington 1789 to Fillmore, 1850; 2214.PR0024 (Box 86)
  - Theodore Frelinghuysen, ca. 1844; 2214.PR0025 (Box 86)
  - Grand Whig Banner, 1844; 2214.PR0026 (Box TBD)
  - Grand National Republican Banner, 1856; 2214.PR0027 (Box 86)
  - John C. Fremont, Republican Candidate, 1856; 2214.PR0028 (Box 86)
  - Gen. James A. Garfield: Republican Candidate, 1880; 2214.PR0029 (Box 86)
  - General U.S. Grant: The Nation's Choice, 1868; 2214.PR0030 (Box 86)
  - General Grant and Family, 1867; 2214.PR0031 (Box 86)
  - National Union Republican Banner, 1868; 2214.PR0032 (Box 101)
  - William Henry Harrison, Ninth President of the United States, ca. 1841; 2214.PR0033 (Box 101)
  - Death of Harrison, April 4 A.D., 1841; 2214.PR0034 (Box 86)
  - Death of Harrison, April 4 A.D., 1841; 2214.PR0035 (Box 86)
  - General William H. Harrison at the Battle of Tippecanoe, 1840; 2214.PR0036 (Box 86)
  - Rutherford B. Hayes, Nineteenth President of the United States, ca. 1876; 2214.PR0037 (Box 86)
  - Andrew Jackson, Seventh President of the United States, 2214.PR0038 (Box 101)
  - Grand Funeral Procession in Memory of General Jackson, ca. 1845; 2214.PR0039 (Box 86)
  - Death of Genl. Andrew Jackson, 1845; 2214.PR0040 (Box 86)
  - Death of Genl. Andrew Jackson, 1845; 2214.PR0041 (Box 86)
  - Andrew Johnson, Seventeenth President of the United States, 2214.PR0042 (Box TBD)
  - Colo. Richd. M. Johnson, ca. 1836; 2214.PR0043 (Box 86)
  - William R. King: Democratic Candidate for Vice President, 1852; 2214.PR0044 (Box 86)
  - The Funeral of President Lincoln, 1865; 2214.PR0045 (Box 86)
  - The Assassination of President Lincoln, 1865; 2214.PR0046 (Box 86)
  - The Presidents of the United States, from 1789 to 1865, ca. 1865; 2214.PR0047 (Box 101)
  - The Death-bed of the Martyr President, Abraham Lincoln, ca. 1865; 2214.PR0048 (Box 86)
  - Death of Abraham Lincoln, ca. 1865; 2214.PR0049 (Box 101)
  - Abraham Lincoln, Sixteenth President of the United States, ca. 1865; 2214.PR0050 (Box 86)
  - Abraham Lincoln, Republican Candidate for Sixteenth President of the United States, ca. 1860; 2214.PR0051 (Box 101)
  - Grand National Democratic Banner, 1864; 2214.PR0052 (Box 86)
  - Majr. Genl. George B. McClellan, The Peoples Choice, 1864; 2214.PR0053 (Box 86)
  - The Brave At Home, ca. 1864; 2214.PR0054 (Box 86)
  - James K. Polk. Eleventh President of the United States, ca. 1845; 2214.PR0055 (Box 86)
  - Grand National Democratic Banner, 1844; 2214.PR0056 (Box 86)
  - James K. Polk. Freedom's Champion, 1848; 2214.PR0057 (Box 86)
  - James K. Polk: The People's Choice, ca. 1844; 2214.PR0058 (Box 101)
  - The Presidents of the United States, 1844; 2214.PR0059 (Box 86)
  - Lewis Cass: Democratic Candidate for 12th President, 1848; 2214.PR0059a (Box 86)
  - The Presidents of the United States, 1844; 2214.PR0060 (Box 86)
  - Lieut. Gen. Winfield Scott, ca. 1852; 2214.PR0061 (Box 89)
  - Death of Genl. Z. Taylor, 12th President of the United States, 1850; 2214.PR0062 (Box 89)
  - The Presidents of the United States, 1848; 2214.PR0063 (Box 89)
  - Genl. Taylor and His Staff on the Morning Before the Battle of Buena Vista, 1847; 2214.PR0064 (Box 89)
  - Genl Z. Taylor and His Battles, 1847; 2214.PR0065 (Box 89)
  - Zachary Taylor / Millard Fillmore, 1848; 2214.PR0066 (Box 89)
  - John Tyler, Tenth President of the United States, 2214.PR0067 (Box 101)
  - Grand Democratic Free Soil Banner, 1848; 2214.PR0068 (Box 101)
  - Martin Van Buren: Eighth President of the United States, 2214.PR0069 (Box 101)
  - Grand, National, American Banner, 1856; 2214.PR0070 (Box 89)
  - Washington's Reception by the Ladies on the Bridge at Trenton, New Jersey, 1848; 2214.PR0071 (Box 89)
  - Washington and His Cabinet, 1876; 2214.PR0072 (Box TBD)
  - Washington Family, 2214.PR0073 (Box 101)
  - Genl. George Washington: Father of his Country, 2214.PR0074 (Box 101)
  - Death of Washington, 1846; 2214.PR0075 (Box 101)
  - Death of Washington. Dec. 14 A.D. 1799, 2214.PR0076 (Box TBD)
  - George Washington. First President of the United States, 2214.PR0077 (Box 89)
  - Washington: First in War, First in Peace, 2214.PR0078 (Box 101)
  - Death of Washington, Dec: 14, A.D. 1799, 2214.PR0079 (Box 89)
  - George Washington, First President of the United States, 2214.PR0080 (Box TBD)
  - Washington's Reception on the Bridge at Trenton, 2214.PR0081 (Box 101)
  - Death of Daniel Webster, ca. 1852-1855; 2214.PR0082 (Box TBD)
  - Prohibition Party leaders of 1884, ca. 1884; 2214.PR0083 (Box 88)
  - General Harrison: The Washington of the West, 1840; 2214.PR0084 (Box TBD)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, ca. 1952; 2214.PR0085 (Box 89)
  - General Grant and His Family, 1866; 2214.PR0086 (Box 88)
  - The Murder of the President - President Arthur and Secretary Blaine, ca. 1881; 2214.PR0087 (Box TBD)
  - The Murder of the President - The Physicians and Surgeons, ca. 1881; 2214.PR0088 (Box TBD)
  - President Cleveland & Cabinet, ca. 1885-1887; 2214.PR0089 (Box TBD)
  - Mother and Son, 1938; 2214.PR0090 (Box 96)
  - Third Ballot made Dewey Unanimous, 1948; 2214.PR0091 (Box 96)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower painted by Norman Rockwell, 1952; 2214.PR0092 (Box 96)
  - President Roosevelt and Party in Royal Gorge, May 8, 1905; 2214.PR0093 (Box 89)
  - Henry Clay, 1843; 2214.PR0094 (Box 88)
  - The Presidents of the United States to, 1885; 2214.PR0095 (Box 88)
  - General William H. Harrison, ca. 1840; 2214.PR0096 (Box 89)
  - General Z. Taylor: "Rough & Ready", 1847; 2214.PR0097 (Box 89)
  - Home of James A. Garfield, Mentor, O., ca. 1880-1881; 2214.PR0098 (Box TBD)
  - Jefferson Davis and Abraham Lincoln, ca. 1864; 2214.PR0099 (Box 89)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, ca. 1952; 2214.PR0100 (Box 89)
  - The Presidents of the United States, 1933; 2214.PR0101 (Box 89)
  - The Republican Convention at Chicago, 1884; 2214.PR0102 (Box 89)
  - A Rare Painting of the Lincoln Family During the Civil War, 2214.PR0103 (Box 96)
  - A Group of Twelve Military Men, ca. 1861; 2214.PR0104 (Box TBD)
  - Death of William Henry Harrison, 1846; 2214.PR0105 (Box 89)
  - President Cleveland and His Cabinet, 1893; 2214.PR0106 (Box 96)
  - The Presidents of Our Great Republic, ca. 1853; 2214.PR0107 (Box TBD)
  - Hon. Stephen A. Douglas, U.S. Senator from Illinois, ca. 1861; 2214.PR0109 (Box 89)
  - John C. Breckinridge, Vice President of the United States, ca. 1856; 2214.PR0110 (Box 89)
  - James K. Polk. The Peoples Candidate for President., 1844; 2214.PR0111 (Box 89)
  - Mr. Lincoln, Residence, and Horse, 1865; 2214.PR0112 (Box 96)
  - Zachary Taylor, Major Genl of the U.S. Army, ca. 1848; 2214.PR0113 (Box TBD)
  - Henry Clay, 1844; 2214.PR0114 (Box 96)
  - Birth-Place of Hon. Stephen A. Douglas, Brandon, Vermont, 1859; 2214.PR0115 (Box TBD)
  - Wilkie Plaster Relief Portrait, ca. 1940; 2214.PR0116 (Box 146)
  - Major Gen. Benj. F. Butler of Massachusetts, ca. 1884; 2214.PR0117 (Box 89)
  - Grand, National, Whig Banner: Press Onward., 1848; 2214.PR0118 (Box 89)
  - Chappaqua Farm, Westchester County, N.Y., 1872; 2214.PR0119 (Box 89)
  - George M. Dallas, Vice President of the United States, 1844; 2214.PR0120 (Box 89)
  - John Quincy Adams, 1844; 2214.PR0121 (Box 89)
  - John Tyler, 1844; 2214.PR0122 (Box 89)
  - James Buchanan, Democratic Candidate for Fifteenth President of the United States, ca. 1856; 2214.PR0123 (Box 89)
  - President McKinley and His Cabinet, 2214.PR0125 (Box 96)
  - President McKinley and His Cabinet, ca. 1897; 2214.PR0125 (Box 96)
  - The Defenders of Our Union, 2214.PR0126 (Box 96)
  - From the Cradle to the Grave, 1881; 2214.PR0127 (Box TBD)
  - The Curse of the Nation, 1882; 2214.PR0128 (Box TBD)
  - William Henry Harrison and Two Soldiers, ca. 1840; 2214.PR0129 (Box TBD)
  - Hon. John P. St. John, ca. 1884; 2214.PR0130 (Box 96)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, ca. 1956; 2214.PR0131 (Box 96)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower Seated at Desk, ca. 1956; 2214.PR0132 (Box 89)
  - Adlai Stevenson, ca. 1956; 2214.PR0133 (Box 89)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, ca. 1956; 2214.PR0134 (Box 89)
  - Richard M. Nixon, ca. 1956; 2214.PR0135 (Box 89)
  - Richard M. Nixon, ca. 1956; 2214.PR0136 (Box 88)
  - The White House Gallery of Official Portraits of the Presidents, 1906; 2214.PR0137 (Box TBD)
  - Stephen A. Douglas, 2214.PR0138 (Box 89)
  - Winfield Scott: The Peoples Choice for Thirteenth President of the United States, 1847; 2214.PR0139 (Box 89)
  - Genl Zachary Taylor: The Hero of Buena Vista., 1848; 2214.PR0140 (Box 89)
  - General Wm. H. Harrison, ca. 1840; 2214.PR0141 (Box TBD)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt, ca. 1943; 2214.PR0142 (Box 89)
  - General Grant & His Family, 1868; 2214.PR0143 (Box TBD)
  - George Washington, 2214.PR0144 (Box 101)
  - Andrew Jackson, President of the United States, 2214.PR0145 (Box 101)
  - The Candidates for the Presidency and Vice Presidency of the United States, 1868; 2214.PR0146 (Box 99)
  - Clasping Hands over the Bloodless (Sar)c(h)asm, 1872; 2214.PR0147 (Box 99)
  - Apollo Amusing the Gods, 1872; 2214.PR0148 (Box 99)
  - "The Pirates" Under False Colors - Can They Capture the Ship of State?, 1872; 2214.PR0149 (Box 99)
  - That "Tidal Wave" - "We are on the Home Stretch!", 1872; 2214.PR0150 (Box 99)
  - The Key-Note of the Campaign, 1872; 2214.PR0151 (Box 99)
  - "Satan, Don't Get Thee Behind Me!" - Any Thing to get Possession, 1872; 2214.PR0152 (Box 99)
  - New York City - The Presidential Election, 1876; 2214.PR0153 (Box 99)
  - Grand Parade and Torchlight Procession in Honor of Tilden and Reform, 1876; 2214.PR0154 (Box TBD)
  - Waiting for an Imaginary Enemy, 1876; 2214.PR0155 (Box 99)
  - New York City - Review by Governor Tilden of the First Division N.Y.S.N.G., 1876; 2214.PR0156 (Box 99)
  - No Change Could Be For The Worse, 1876; 2214.PR0157 (Box TBD)
  - Missouri - The Democratic National Convention, 1876; 2214.PR0158 (Box 99)
  - Ohio - The Republican National Convention at Cincinnati, 1876; 2214.PR0159 (Box TBD)
  - Philadelphia, PA - The Centennial Exposition, 1876; 2214.PR0160 (Box 99)
  - Missouri - The Great Whiskey Ring Trial, 1876; 2214.PR0161 (Box 99)
  - Grand Larceny vs. Petty Larceny; Or, Political Justice Exemplified, 1872; 2214.PR0162 (Box 99)
  - Grant's First and Last Vote, 1872; 2214.PR0163 (Box 99)
  - New York City - Obsequies of the Late Horace Greeley, 1872; 2214.PR0164 (Box 99)
  - "Look Here, Upon This Picture. And On This.", 1872; 2214.PR0165 (Box TBD)
  - The Modern Moses to his People, 1872; 2214.PR0166 (Box 99)
  - At the Bar of Public Opinion, 1872; 2214.PR0167 (Box 99)
  - Hon. Horace Greeley, 1872; 2214.PR0168 (Box 99)
  - Maryland - The National Democratic Convention, 1872; 2214.PR0169 (Box 99)
  - On To Philadelphia; or, The March of the Bread and Butter Brigade, 1872; 2214.PR0170 (Box 99)
  - Ohio - The Cincinnati Convention of Liberal Republicans, 1872; 2214.PR0171 (Box 99)
  - New York City - The Great Mass Meeting of Liberal Republicans, 1872; 2214.PR0172 (Box 99)
  - Our Modern Belshazzar, 1872; 2214.PR0173 (Box 99)
  - Grand Torchlight Procession of the Wide-Awake Clubs in the City of New York, 1860; 2214.PR0174 (Box TBD)
  - The High Court of Impeachment, 1868; 2214.PR0175 (Box 99)
  - Grand Reception of the Notabilities of the Nation at the White House, 1865; 2214.PR0176 (Box 88)
- Series XIII. Ribbons
  Ribbons: This series contains a variety of badges, most of which are at least in part textiles. Some of the items are still associated with their original metal pins.
  - Bell-Everett Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1860; 2214.RB0001 (Box 123)
  - Fort Wayne, Indiana, Blaine Club Ribbon, 1892; 2214.RB0002 (Box 123)
  - Blaine Welcome Ribbon, 1888; 2214.RB0003 (Box 123)
  - Blaine-Logan Plumed Helmet Campaign Ribbon, 1884; 2214.RB0004 (Box 123)
  - Blaine Club of Philadelphia Ribbon, ca. 1888; 2214.RB0005 (Box 123)
  - Blaine-Logan "Business Men's Parade" Ribbon, ca. 1884; 2214.RB0006 (Box 123)
  - Blaine, Logan, Lincoln, Garfield, and Washington Portrait Ribbon, ca. 1884; 2214.RB0007 (Box 123)
  - Blaine Reception Ribbon, 1888; 2214.RB0008 (Box 135)
  - Blaine Portrait Button with Ribbon, ca. 1892; 2214.RB0009 (Box 123)
  - Bryan-Sewall Portrait Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1896; 2214.RB0010 (Box 123)
  - Bryan-Stevenson Campaign Bookmark, ca. 1900; 2214.RB0011 (Box 100)
  - "For President: Wm. J. Bryan" Portrait Button and Ribbon, ca. 1896-1908; 2214.RB0012 (Box 167)
  - Buchanan-Breckinridge Portrait Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1856; 2214.RB0013 (Box 123)
  - Buchanan-Breckinridge Portrait Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1856; 2214.RB0014 (Box 123)
  - Bulkeley Vice-Presidential Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1896; 2214.RB0015 (Box 123)
  - Clay-Frelinghuysen Essex Delegation Ribbon, 1844; 2214.RB0016 (Box 123)
  - Henry Clay "Champion of the American System" Ribbon, ca. 1844; 2214.RB0017 (Box 123)
  - Henry Clay "Pride of America" Ribbon, ca. 1844; 2214.RB0018 (Box 123)
  - Henry Clay "O.K. / Oll For Klay" Ribbon, 1844; 2214.RB0019 (Box 123)
  - Clay-Frelinghuysen "The People's Choice" Ribbon, ca. 1844; 2214.RB0020 (Box 123)
  - Clay-Frelinghuysen "The People's Choice" Ribbon, ca. 1844; 2214.RB0021 (Box 123)
  - Clay-Frelinghuysen "Protection" Portrait Ribbon, ca. 1844; 2214.RB0022 (Box 123)
  - Clay-Frelinghuysen Portrait Ribbon, ca. 1844; 2214.RB0023 (Box 123)
  - Henry Clay "The Nation's Favorite" Ribbon, ca. 1844; 2214.RB0024 (Box 124)
  - Henry Clay Whig Convention Ribbon, 1844; 2214.RB0025 (Box 124)
  - Henry Clay "Rhode Island Line" Whig Convention Ribbon, 1844; 2214.RB0026 (Box 124)
  - Henry Clay "Faithful Even Unto Death" Memorial Ribbon, ca. 1852; 2214.RB0027 (Box 124)
  - Henry Clay Memorial Ribbon, ca. 1852; 2214.RB0028 (Box 124)
  - Coolidge-Dawes-Fredericks Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1924; 2214.RB0029 (Box 124)
  - James M. Cox Campaign Badge/Pennant, ca. 1920; 2214.RB0030 (Box 124)
  - Cleveland Club of Philadelphia Portrait Ribbon, 2214.RB0031 (Box 124)
  - Cleveland-Hendricks Tammany Hall Campaign Ribbon, 1884; 2214.RB0032 (Box 124)
  - Cleveland World's Industrial and Cotton Centennial Exposition Ribbon, ca. 1884-1885; 2214.RB0033 (Box 124)
  - 9th Assembly District Cleveland and Hendricks Campaign Club Ribbon, ca. 1884; 2214.RB0034 (Box 124)
  - Cleveland Portrait Campaign Ribbon, 2214.RB0035 (Box 124)
  - Cleveland "Democratic Candidate" Portrait Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1884-1892; 2214.RB0036 (Box 124)
  - Cleveland Portrait Campaign Ribbon, 2214.RB0037 (Box 124)
  - New York Stock Exchange Cleveland & Hendricks Club Ribbon, 1884; 2214.RB0038 (Box 124)
  - Gloucester County, New Jersey, German Democratic League Ribbon, 2214.RB0039 (Box 124)
  - Cleveland Neptune Township Democratic Club Portrait Ribbon, 2214.RB0040 (Box 124)
  - Cleveland-Hendricks Portrait Inaugural Ribbon, 1885; 2214.RB0041 (Box 124)
  - Cleveland-Hendricks Portrait Inaugural Ribbon, 1885; 2214.RB0042 (Box 124)
  - "Cleveland and Hendricks Committee" Ribbon, ca. 1884; 2214.RB0043 (Box 135)
  - Cleveland "Jeffersonian Club" Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1892; 2214.RB0044 (Box 124)
  - Cleveland-Thurman Tarrytown Democratic Club Campaign Ribbon, 1888; 2214.RB0045 (Box 135)
  - Cleveland-Thurman "Democratic Candidates" Portrait Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1888; 2214.RB0046 (Box 124)
  - New York Stock Exchange Cleveland and Thurman Club Ribbon, 1888; 2214.RB0047 (Box 135)
  - New York Stock Exchange Cleveland and Thurman Club Ribbon, 1888; 2214.RB0048 (Box 135)
  - Utica, New York, Cleveland Guards Portrait Ribbon, ca. 1884-1892; 2214.RB0049 (Box 124)
  - Cleveland Portrait Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1884-1892; 2214.RB0050 (Box 125)
  - "Kansas Redeemed, Populism Dead" Ribbon, ca. 1896; 2214.RB0051 (Box 125)
  - Frances Folsom Cleveland "Victory United Democracy 1892" Portrait Ribbon, 2214.RB0052 (Box 125)
  - Cleveland "Victory United Democracy 1892" Portrait Ribbon, 2214.RB0053 (Box 125)
  - Cleveland National Democratic Convention Ribbon, 1892; 2214.RB0054 (Box 125)
  - Cleveland National Democratic Convention Ribbon, 1892; 2214.RB0055 (Box 125)
  - New York Stock Exchange Cleveland & Stevenson Club Vice President Ribbon, 1892; 2214.RB0057 (Box 125)
  - New York Stock Exchange Cleveland & Stevenson Club Ribbon, 1892; 2214.RB0058 (Box 125)
  - Cleveland Inaugural Ribbon, 1893; 2214.RB0059 (Box 125)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson Campaign Ribbon, 1892; 2214.RB0060 (Box 125)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson Inaugural Ribbon, 1893; 2214.RB0061 (Box 125)
  - Tammany Hall National Democratic Convention Ribbon, 1892; 2214.RB0062 (Box 125)
  - "Democratic Watcher" Ribbon, 1892; 2214.RB0063 (Box 125)
  - Cleveland National Democratic Convention Ribbon, 1892; 2214.RB0064 (Box 135)
  - New York Stock Exchange Cleveland & Stevenson Club Secretary Ribbon, 1892; 2214.RB0065 (Box 125)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson "Our Choice" Portrait Ribbon, ca. 1892; 2214.RB0066 (Box 208)
  - New York Business Men's Cleveland & Stevenson Clubs Inaugural Ribbon, 1893; 2214.RB0067 (Box 135)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson 11th Ward Democratic Club Ribbon, ca. 1892; 2214.RB0068 (Box 125)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson Tammany Hall Inaugural Ribbon, 1893; 2214.RB0069 (Box 135)
  - "President Cleveland, 1892-1896" Portrait Ribbon, ca. 1892-1896; 2214.RB0070 (Box 125)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson Committe on Inaugural Ceremonies Ribbon, 1893; 2214.RB0072 (Box 125)
  - Mercer County Democracy Club Ribbon, ca. 1892; 2214.RB0073 (Box 135)
  - "For President: Grover Cleveland" Ribbon, ca. 1884-1892; 2214.RB0074 (Box 125)
  - Set of Ten Presidential Commemorative Ribbons, ca. 1893; 2214.RB0075 (Box 125)
  - John W. Davis Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1924; 2214.RB0076 (Box 125)
  - Debs Campaign Ribbon, 1912; 2214.RB0077 (Box 136)
  - Debs-Seidel "Our Candidates" Portrait Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1912; 2214.RB0078 (Box 125)
  - New York County Socialist Party Ribbon, ca. 1900-1920; 2214.RB0079 (Box 125)
  - Socialist Party Ribbon, ca. 1900-1920; 2214.RB0080 (Box 125)
  - Socialist Party German Branch Committee Ribbon, 1916; 2214.RB0081 (Box 126)
  - "Draft Dewey" Paper Badge, ca. 1948; 2214.RB0082 (Box 199)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Inaugural Committee Medal and Ribbon, 1953; 2214.RB0083 (Box 126)
  - Eisenhower "We Like Ike!" Portrait Ribbon, ca. 1952; 2214.RB0084 (Box 126)
  - Eisenhower Paper Badge, ca. 1952; 2214.RB0085 (Box 100)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Ribbon, ca. 1952; 2214.RB0086 (Box 126)
  - Republican Party "Official Challenger" Ribbons, 1952; 2214.RB0087 (Box 126)
  - Fillmore-Donelson Portrait Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1856; 2214.RB0089 (Box 126)
  - Frémont-Dayton Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1856; 2214.RB0090 (Box 126)
  - Frémont-Dayton Commemorative Portrait Button and Ribbon, 2214.RB0091 (Box 135)
  - Garfield Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1880; 2214.RB0092 (Box 126)
  - "Garfield and Arthur, The People's Choice" Song Lyric Textile, ca. 1880; 2214.RB0093 (Box 126)
  - Wholesale Dry Goods and Carpet Association Garfield Portrait Ribbon, ca. 1880; 2214.RB0094 (Box 126)
  - Garfield "In Memoriam, Our President" Ribbon, ca. 1881; 2214.RB0095 (Box 126)
  - Garfield "We Mourn For Our President" Ribbon, ca. 1881; 2214.RB0096 (Box 126)
  - "In Memoriam: Jas. A. Garfield" Portrait Ribbon, 1881; 2214.RB0097 (Box 187)
  - Garfield "We Honored Him In Life ..." Ribbon, ca. 1881; 2214.RB0098 (Box 126)
  - "In Memory of James A. Garfield" Ribbon, ca. 1881; 2214.RB0100 (Box 126)
  - "U.S. Grant, Pride of America" Ribbon, ca. 1868; 2214.RB0101 (Box 126)
  - "General Grant, Our Next President" Ribbon, ca. 1868; 2214.RB0102 (Box 126)
  - Set of Four "For President: Gen. U.S. Grant" Ribbons, ca. 1868; 2214.RB0103 (Box 126)
  - Grant-Wilson "15th Ward Republican Ticket" Ribbon, ca. 1872; 2214.RB0104 (Box 127)
  - "General Grant, President" Ribbon, ca. 1872; 2214.RB0105 (Box 127)